# Daniel Grinshpon

9714 North Pond Circle, Roswell GA 30076 (404) 578 - 6879 GrinshponDaniel@protonmail.com https://github.com/Grinshpon https://gitlab.com/Grinshpon

## Objective

Mostly self-taught programmer with 3+ years of experience looking to expand my knowledge of computer science and engineering, as well as apply my skills by finding research or career opportunities. Looking for programming position involved with software engineering, programming, data analysis, automation.

### Experience

Computer Game Programming:

Space Warp: First real project was a game made for the FBLA competition in 2016. It was the first time I had to deal with a deadline, using a graphics framework and development environment. It was a simple Asteroids clone.

Running Low: Game prototype in 72 hours during the Ludum Dare jam, completely from scratch, using the Love2d framework. In the game you have to move and fire projectiles at an endless wave of enemies. https://ldjam.com/events/ludum-dare/43/running-low

Mobile App Development:

Epee Bout Tool: Scoring and timekeeping tool for fencing matches, or bouts. Used CoronaSDK, and published it on the Google Play Store. I made this mainly for my high school's fencing team, of which I was a part of.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.HCl.Epee\_Bout\_Tool Calculator Program:

\* Markov: Simplistic algebra tool written in Haskell. Made as a way for me to learn and practice different concepts in programming and in Haskell, such as parsing, maps, state monads. https://gitlab.com/Grinshpon/markov

### Technical Summary

Languages: Java, C#, C, C++, Lua, Haskell, HTML, LaTeX. Other Software: Unity, Corona SDK, Love2d Operating Systems: Windows, Linux (Debian, Mint)

### Skills

I possess qualities in rational thought and logical problem solving. I have a well-rounded knowledge of algorithms and an ability to quickly learn computer languages and syntax. I can effectively communicate to a team and perform risk assessment thanks to my experience working as a lifeguard and restaurant supervisor.

### Education

North Springs Charter High School, GPA 3.2

Advanced Placement Computer Science Course: 2015-2016, AP Score: 5

Advanced Placement Calculus BC: 2016-2017, AP Score: 4

Georgia State University

Principles of Computer Science II 1302: Fall 2018

Multivariate Calculus 2215: Fall 2018 Principles of Physics I 2211: Fall 2018

### Work Experience

Jones Bridge Pizza:

Management: supervising and cooperating with employees as cook, 2018 Customer Service: Communicating between customers and kitchen, 2016-2018

**Sweetwater Pools:** 

**Lifeguard:** Watching over crowds, assessing for safety hazards, 2016

#### Activities

Computer Science Club, Member: 2014-2018

Vice President: 2017-2018

Future Business Leaders of America Competition: 2015-2016

**Fencing club:** 2016-2018 **COMAP:** 2016, 2017